Guide to the Native American oral histories audio recordings 1954-1993
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Ute - Mountain Ute contract series II
  - Nedra Kuebler, 1991 January 09; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 16)
  - Charles Knight, 1991 January 09; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 17)
  - Sarah Hatch, 1991 January 09; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 18)
  - Effie Hemp Root, 1991 January 10; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 19)
  - James Root, >1991 January 10; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 20)
  - Annie Cantsee, >1991 January 10; Audiocassette (Cassette UMT Crt. 21)
- White Mesa Ute project
  - Pochief Mike, 1980 March 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 1)
    Reel-to-Reel A-Tape
    There is also an A-Cass Tape Duplicate available for patron use.
  - Chester Cantsee, 1980 March 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 2)
  - Willie Lehi, 1980 March 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 3)
  - Anna Lee Duchie, 1980 May 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 4)
  - Mayers Cantsee, 1980 May 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 5)
  - Milly Mike, 1980 May 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 6)
  - Anna Marie Nat, 1980 May 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 7)
  - Joyce Lehi Posey, 1980 May 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 8)
  - Jennie Lehi Posey, 1980 May 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 9)
  - Pete Bishop, 1980 May 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 10)
  - Joe Leigh, 1980 May 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 11)
  - Sarah Owl, 1980 May 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 12)
  - Lola Nelson Mike, 1980 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 13)
  - Stella Eyetoo, 1980 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 14)
  - Wahlella Laner Begay, 1980 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 15)
  - Dan W. Lehi, 1980 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 16)
  - Zelma Black Acton, 1980 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 17)
  - Mary Cantsee May, 1980 August 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 18)
  - Patty M. Dutchie, 1980 August 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 19)
  - Nedra Ketchum, 1980 August 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 20)
  - Helen Lang, 1980 August 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 21)
  - Bonnie Mike Lehi, 1980 August 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel WMU 22)
  - Patty M. Dutchie, 1983 August 09; Audiocassette (Cassette WMU 23a-b)
    White Mesa.
  - Adeline Eyetoo, Stella Eyetoo, 1983 August 09; Audiocassette (Cassette WMU 24)
  - Raymond Lopez, 1984 February 23; Audiocassette (Cassette WMU 25)
    Interviewed and recorded by Rose Ann Mills Silas
  - Hall Taylor Towaoc, 1984 February 02; Audiocassette (Cassette WMU 26)
    Interviewed and recorded by LaVerna Summer and Rose Ann Mills Silas
  - Paul Ute Towaoc, 1984 February 02; Audiocassette (Cassette WMU 27)